in entrepreneurial activity.
An entrepreneur examines needs, wants, and problems, and then tries to think about if
a better solution can be created.
Narrows the possible opportunities down to one specific opportunity.
Thinks of an innovative idea to address the identified opportunity, researches the opportunity
and idea thoroughly, enlists the best experts, sources of advice and assistance that can be
found, plans the venture and looks for possible problems that might arise, and weighs
the risks and possible rewards before making a
decision.
Never gets tied to a specific idea, even if they personally love it, if research shows
it's not likely to work.
Employs the resources necessary for the venture if the decision is made to go ahead.
Understands that any entrepreneurial venture will take a great deal of long, hard work.
Realizes a sense of accomplishment from successful ventures and learns lessons for the
future.
One of the biggest things that leads to success as an entrepreneur is ensuring you've identified